<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Sunburst</string>
    <string name="being1">The term being means either the totality of the real, or that in a thing which makes it to be a being, e.g., "the being of a thing". However, a being, with an article, is a that which is.</string>
    <string name="being2">The being of a being, that is, the “is”-ness of a being, is the most fundamental of its attributes, which presents it as radically present to the world, and which it shares with all other beings, forming reality.</string>
    <string name="being3">Beings fall into two orders: real and mental. Real being is that which is present “out there”, in extramental reality. A real being can be a complete being in itself, or any part of a real being. Mental being is that which is present only within an idea, e.g. abstractions, mental constructs, dreams. We will be concerning ourselves with real being throughout this inquiry.</string>
    <string name="transcendentals1">There are five transcendentals, or attributes that can be predicated of every real being. Being is one, and the others are one, active, good, and true. These attributes are coextensive with being: according to the measure and manner in which a thing possesses being, it partakes of unity, truth, activity, and goodness. Conversely, according to the measure and manner in which a thing shares in these attributes, it possesses being. Taken together they reveal the full richness of being, like many facets of the same diamond, turned different ways. </string>
    <string name="transcendentals2">When we perceive any object, we perceive it as something united in itself, distinct from other beings. One signifies this inner act of cohering, of holding itself together as a unified whole, as separated from every other. To be is thus to act as a unit. </string>
    <string name="transcendentals3">Activity signifies every being’s tendency to communicate itself and to express its own nature through its characteristic activities. Beings naturally proliferate and connect up with each other through action to form an interacting system of beings acting on and being acted on by each other. If there was a being that did not act, it might as well not be. To be is thus to be actively present to other real beings. </string>
    <string name="transcendentals4">Good signifies the intrinsic value in every being, as apt to be desired, enjoyed, or appreciated in some way by another being. Every being, because it has some degree of real existence of its own, stands out from the darkness of non-being, and is to be valued as such. To be is thus to be good.</string>
    <string name="transcendentals5">Good implies the relation of some valuer: a good for something (which could be itself). But the good in beings does not have to be consciously valued (a positive tendency towards it is enough), or actually valued at all, but merely apt to be valued, so long as it exists.</string>
    <string name="transcendentals6">As Good implies the relation of some valuer, True implies the relation of some intellect. It signifies the knowability of every being, as ordered by its very nature, on the basis of its existence, to be understood. A thing is knowable insofar as it exists: the more there is to know, the more there can be known.</string>
</resources>